[ 	{
		"question": "The wine list at our restaurant is _____",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "regressive"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "agressive"},
			{ "id":2, "text": "progressive"},
			{ "id":3, "text": "transgressive"}

		],
		"correct":2,
		"feedback" : "Wine is listed in sequential order starting with the sweetest and most mild wine progressing to the fuller and drier in taste wines."
	},
	{
		"question": "What question would you ask a guest who orders a martini?",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "Gin or vodka?"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "Up or on the rocks?"},
			{ "id":2, "text": "Olives or lemon twist?"},
			{ "id":3, "text": "All of the above"}

		],
		"correct":3

	},
	{
		"question": "A frozen blend of tropical fruit flavors mixed with Captain Morgan Original Spiced Rum and topped with a splash of Bacardi Black rum.",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "Berry Mango Daiquiri"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "Bahama Mama"},
			{ "id":2, "text": "Pina Colada"},
			{ "id":3, "text": "Mudslide"}

		],
		"correct":1

	},
	{
		"question": "Light to medium-bodied wine with flavors of lime, green apple, passion fruit and white peach",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "Chardonnay"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "Merlot"},
			{ "id":2, "text": "Riesling"},
			{ "id":3, "text": "Sauvignon Blanc"}

		],
		"correct":3

	},
	{
		"question": "Our well vodka is Absolut",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "True"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "False"}
			
		],
		"correct":1,
		"feedback":"Our well vodka is Smirnoff"

	},
	{
		"question": "Alotta Colada is served with a sidecar of _____ ",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "Southern Comfort"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "Disarono Amaretto"},
			{ "id":2, "text": "Captain Morgan Spiced Rum"},
			{ "id":3, "text": "Grand Marnier"}
			
		],
		"correct":2,
		"feedback":"Alotta Colada is served with sidecar of Captain Morgan Spiced Rum"

	},
	{
		"question": "What is true about red and white Zinfandels?",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "White Zinfandel wine has a pale rose color, while a red Zinfandel has a deep red, almost black color"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "A white Zinfandel's flavor is very sweet, while a red Zinfandel's flavor is spicy and peppery"},
			{ "id":2, "text": "Made from Zinfandel grape"},
			{ "id":3, "text": "All of the above"}
			
		],
		"correct":3
		
	},
	{
		"question": "We have the following IPA(s)",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "Lagunitas"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "Stone"},
			{ "id":2, "text": "Ballast Point"},
			{ "id":3, "text": "All of the above"}
			
		],
		"correct":0
		
	},
	{
		"question": "Our sparkling wine(s) are?",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "Lambrusco"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "La Marca"},
			{ "id":2, "text": "Corbel Brut"},
			{ "id":3, "text": "All of the above"}
			
		],
		"correct":1
		
	},
	{
		"question": "Malibu Red, pinapple juice, mango passion fruit mix topped with Bacardi Black Rum",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "Mai Tai"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "High Tide"},
			{ "id":2, "text": "Lobster Punch"},
			{ "id":3, "text": "Red Lobster Sunset"}
			
		],
		"correct":2
		
	},
	{
		"question": "Our house Chardonnay is ______",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "SeaGlass Unoaked"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "Kendal-Jackson"},
			{ "id":2, "text": "La Crema"},
			{ "id":3, "text": "Sutter Home"}
			
		],
		"correct":3
		
	},
	{
		"question": "The recent Core Menu change discontinued Shrimp Wreck Mary drink because we do not carry Stoli vodka anymore",
		"answers": [
			{ "id":0, "text": "True"},
			{ "id":1, "text": "False"}
			
		],
		"correct":1,
		"feedback":"Shrimp Wreck Mary is made with Absolut vodka and garnished with coctail shrip.  It is a great upsell for Blody Mary!"
		
	}
]